

### **SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- React.js
- Vue.js
- Sass
- Bootstrap
- Node.js

### PERSONAL SKILLS

Creative spirit
Organized
Time management
Team player
Fast learner
Motivated

# CONTACT

P: +358 44 9818473

E: cihanerenler@outlook.com W: <u>www.cihanerenler.com</u>

L: <u>linkedin.com/in/cihanerenler</u>

# CIHAN ERENLER

# JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER

#### **ABOUT**

I am a junior front-end developer who is currently a second-year IT student at HAMK, in Finland. I am proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React. In addition, I have experience working with Vue.js and Node.js. I have studied and graduated as an art teacher from my prior education, where I honed my graphic design skills.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT TRAINEE F-Secure | May 2021 - Dec 2021

- Improving and debugging design system components
- Developing Vue components
- Improving UX

# CHILDREN BOOK ILLUSTRATOR Nuori 2000 Pori | Feb 2018 - Aug 2018

- Illustrating children books
- Designing posters
- In events working as photographer

### **EDUCATION**

### **COMPUTER APPLICATIONS**

Hame University of Applied Sciences - Finland | 2020 - Current

# **BACHELOR OF ART TEACHING**

Cukurova University - Turkey | 2013 - 2016

### **PROJECTS**

www.cihanerenler.com/#projects